<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Perce</string>
    <string name="username">username"</string>
    <string name="password">password"</string>
    <string name="open">open</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>
    <string name="doupletap">Click back again to exit application</string>
    <string name="lorem_ipsum">Perce is an online bookstore with a mission to financially support local, independent bookstores.
We believe that bookstores are essential to a healthy culture. They’re where authors can connect with readers, where we discover new writers, where children get hooked on the thrill of reading that can last a lifetime. They’re also anchors for our downtowns and communities.
As more and more people buy their books online, we wanted to create an easy, convenient way for you to get your books and support bookstores at the same time.
    We also support anyone who advocates for books through our affiliate program, which pays a 10% commission on every sale, and gives a matching 10% to independent bookstores. If you are an author, a website or magazine, have a bookclub, an organization that wants to recommend books, or even just a book-lover with an Instagram feed, you can sign up to be an affiliate, start your own shop, and be rewarded for your advocacy of books. Perce wants to give back to everyone who promotes books, authors, and independent bookstores!
By design, we give away over 75% of our profit margin to stores, publications, authors and others who make up the thriving, inspirational culture around books!
We hope that Perce can help strengthen the fragile ecosystem and margins around bookselling and keep local bookstores an integral part of our culture and communities.
Perce is a benefit corporation - a corporation dedicated to the public good.
    </string>
    <string name="supplement_hint">Search for supplement...</string>
    <string name="aboutUs">About Us</string>
    <string name="logIn">Log In</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="title1">Current Plan</string>
    <string name="title2">Allowed Foods</string>
    <string name="notify">Notifications</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset checked supplements</string>
    <string name="dark">Dark theme</string>
    <string name="user_info_key">userInfo</string>
    <string name="enter_credentials">Please enter your credentials</string>
    <string name="foodItemHint">Search for food item...</string>
    <string name="channel_name">channel name</string>
    <string name="channel_description">channel description</string>
    <string name="channel_id">channel id</string>
    <string name="notification_text">Don\'t forget your vitamins. Stay hidrated and have a great day!</string>
    <string name="reminder">Reminder</string>
    <string name="old_pass">Current password</string>
    <string name="new_pass1">New password</string>
    <string name="new_pass2">Confirm new password</string>
    <string name="forgotPassword">Forgot password?</string>
    <string name="change_password">Change password</string>
    <string name="email">email</string>
</resources>